Stelling, John D. and Valerie C. Collection of Sanford Thompson Files 6217
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
John D. and Valerie C. Stelling Collection of Sanford Thompson Files
1898- 1932
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Thompson, Sanford
Stelling, John D.
Stelling, Valerie C.
6217
4 cubic feet
4 linear ft.
Records.
6179236
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
D. Mordente, March 04, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 04, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5615: Sanford E. Thompson Papers
Construction industry -- New England; Cement industries -- New England; Masonry -- New England; Earthwork -- New England; New England -- Economic policy; Stelling, John D.; Stelling, Valerie C.; Thompson, Sanford E. (Sanford Eleazer), 1867- 1949.; Downington Iron Works; New England Council; Roland Park Company
6179236
- Downingtown Iron Works Report on Overhead (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Downingtown Iron Works Report- 1932 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Downingtown Iron Works Report- 1931, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- New England Industrial Survey (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Downingtown Iron Works Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Original 1898 Sheets on Shoveling Study (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Plastering PL A,B,C,D,E,F (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Plastering PL G,H,I,J,K (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Chapters on Management Book (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Chapters on Management Book 2 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Chapters on Management Book 3 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Balance of Store- Tabor Co. 1913 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Earthwork Chapters (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Earthwork Chapters 2 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Earthwork Trenching by Hand (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Earthwork- Stationary Machinery Tables Cost- (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Earthwork- Wheelbarrow (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Earthwork- Train equipment Tables Costs- (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Earthwork- Wet Machine Tables Costs- (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Earthwork- (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Rock Excavation RE B,C (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Rock Excavation RE D,E (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Roland Park Co.-Sidewalks (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Roland Park Co.-Excavation (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Roland Park Co.- Houses & Buildings (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Sheeting & Bracing (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Shoring Underpinning (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Slating SLA, SLB, SLC (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Slating SLD, SLE (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Slating SLF, WB (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Snow Removal Sn B, C (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Stone Masonry SM B,C (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Stone Masonry SM D, E (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Stone Cutting SC D (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Street Cleaning St. Cl. C, D (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Track Laying TL C, TL D (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Tar Roofing & Waterproofing TR & WB, TR & WC (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Trenching 1 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Trenching 2 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Wire Lathing WiL A, C (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Woodworking (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Wood Lathing WoL A, B (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Taylor Society 1921-1924 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Taylor Society 1924-1927 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Taylor Society New England Division (Box 2, Folder 30)
- 1920 Tables Complete (Box 3, Folder 1)
- 1920 Tables Complete 2 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Bookkeeping Under The Taylor System (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Cost Accounting (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Labor LNA, LNC (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Paving WB 15 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Paving PAV B (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Paving PAV C (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Paving PAV D (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Earthwork EWE MSS (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Earthwork- Erath Pressure EC (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Earthwork- Excavation Work Papers (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Piece Work 1 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Piece Work 2 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Pile Driving PD B,C,D (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Pipe Laying PLB,C (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Earthwork Trainwork (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Earthwork- Time Studies Wheelbarrow (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Misc. Materials Relative to Tests (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Tests (Box 3, Folder 20)
- C.H. Newhall (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Hugh Nawn Contracting Co. (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Springfield Contractors Supply Co. (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Simpson Brothers Co. (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Questionnaires (Box 3, Folder 25)
- B.B. Shedd (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Sayles Bleacheries- Tests, Studies (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Misc. Tests (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Cart Work Data on Costs of Mules & Horses (Box 4, Folder 1)
- PLB 965 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Plastering PL L,M,O,Z (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Rip Rap RR C,D (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Earthwork- (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Earthwork- Cart Work & Work Papers (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Coal Photos, Hoar Shovel Company (Pottsville, PA 1924) (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Carpentry (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Book Outlines (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Hopewell Railway Supply (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Chapter 22- Budgetary Control (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Chapter 20- Relating Wages to the Job (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Chapter 19- Job Analysis & Time Study (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Chapter 17/23- Cost & Cost Control (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Chapter 16- Relating Wages to Production (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Chapter 15- Time Study & Job Analysis (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Chapter 14- The Management Movement (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Chapter 12- Chapter on Organization (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Chapter 10- The Financial Department (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Chapter 9- Manufacturing (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Chapter 8- Dept. of Industrial Relations (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Chapter 7- Storeskeeping (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Chapter 6- Purchasing (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Chapter 5- Engineering (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Chapter 4- Traffic & Shipping (Box 4, Folder 25)